Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
After hearing Yami's tale about how never giving up can open new doors, Asta was filled with fresh resolve to face his rival.
Alright! Time to work hard, catch up to Yuno, and leave him behind!
Just then.
Damn! That's the biggest outlet I've ever heard.
Quit banging the door down! If you're looking for Captain Yami's black bullet, then you came to the ra-
Whoa! What just happened?
Hey, I recognize her!
That's Poigolian's sister!
ev Cat
You can spot your toes
And make all those guys
I'll see you soon now.
We'll be right back, we'll be right back, we'll be right back.
Dude, what is this about? Is the captain of the Crimson Lion Kings really here?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, Captain, why are you showing up on our doorstep out of nowhere?
It's Mara Leona!
Hey, why is it so damn noisy in here all of a sudden?
Sheesh, can't a guy even take a dump? Oh.
Dangerous animal on the loose!
Everybody, hurry up and get out of the building now!
No! Trust me, if you get caught, just play dead!
Don't make eye contact, you're it'll eat you! Ow!
Shut up and take this, moron.
What is it? Let me guess, it's some kind of poison drink that'll tear holes in my throat and make me spit fireballs, right?
It's for visiting my brother! Do you have a death wish?
I don't need a thank you present for that. Besides, if this is what a beast like you drinks, I guarantee it's not fit for human consumption.
Don't want it.
Then I'll kill you!
So you came here to thank me and you've already moved on to killing me?
I'll thank you, then kill you!
Man, you do not joke around!
That's because I hate jokes!
Captain, you sure you don't want this?
Fine.
I'll take it.
Oh, I understand now. You're only here to talk to Captain Yami, that's all.
What a relief. In here, I thought I was about to get dragged off to somewhere crazy again.
You three, come with me!
I don't like this! Where are we going? Somewhere bad, I just know it!
Wait!
Why am I getting dragged off to?
Maybe there's gonna be a fight!
I just need to go into it, I guess you're heading out, though.
Hey, Captain! This mad woman is trying to kidnap three of your squad members! Don't you think you should do something?
As long as she leaves, she can do whatever she wants!
Whatever she wants! If you don't help us, we're gonna be far with you!
Come on, Captain, you can't let her do that!
If it's only you three she wants, then you guys must have done something really rotten!
You deserve this, especially you, Luck!
These are the squad members who passed the Royal Knights selection exam.
We made it?
So we're in the Royal Knights?
That means even though I lost the tournament, Yuno didn't get ahead of me!
We're still neck and neck in the race to be the next Wizard King!
This is great!
Yay!
I'm so happy I made the cut!
Now Asta and I can finally...
I mean, not that I care about anything like that!
I'm glad Asta passed the exam, but only because I'm proud of him as a squadmate!
That's all he is to me, really!
Nothing more and nothing less!
End of story!
Hey, Noelle!
We're gonna be awesome Royal Knights!
Yeah, sure.
Just don't rush in on your own again and ruin things for the rest of us.
I won't, but I've been training super hard, so it'll still turn out okay if I do.
Idiot!
What part of don't do it did you not understand?
Sorry!
Actually, wait.
There was supposed to be one more Black Bull who made the Royal Knights.
Really?
There's one more?
Um, I'm sure it was probably me.
Over here!
Pick me!
I don't see him.
I'm right behind you!
It's Magna's ring of the Black Bulls here!
It isn't you!
Oh, well.
He received his summons.
I didn't pass after all.
Man, that's rough.
Aw, too bad for you, Magna.
Working with the Royal Knights is gonna make me even stronger, so you probably won't be a match for me anymore.
Hold on, Luck.
Be careful what you say.
Rub it in my face all you want to, jerk!
If I fall down seven times, I'll get up eight times.
I just hope that you won't be too intimidated by how buff and awesome I am when you come back to the hideout.
All right, time to start on my training.
Let's do this fun mess, huh?
Me?
But I was just about to pop open this booze.
I want to get stronger and pronto!
No, I have to get stronger.
Well, if you insist, I guess I can make time for you, Mr. Delinquent.
I'm not a delinquent!
Better say your prayers, Luck, and, uh, come back here in one piece.
Sure!
The same goes for you guys.
Gotcha!
Obviously.
Your friends have been cheering for me.
Huh!
Look at him.
Smiles all around.
Give him hell.
From the Silver Eagles, Nils Ruggas!
Here!
The Vice Captain of the Coral Peacocks!
Where is Kirsch Vermillion?
Ugh!
I never tire of hearing the beautiful melody that is my name.
From the Blue Rose Knights, we have Pooley Angel in the flesh!
What do you say, folks?
Did you miss me?
Because I'm back!
And Rheingard of the Green Praying Mantises!
Yes!
I'm fired up!
Let's put the Mush in Mushroom!
Yay!
Representing the Aqua Deer, Captain Rill Bormortier, as well as Fragile Tormenta!
Here!
Yup!
That's me!
I'm the failure who lost, even though he's a captain!
Please, sir!
Now's the time to dig deep and stay strong!
And from the Golden Dawn, Hammond Cassius, Klaus Lunettes, Mimosa Vermillion, and Huno!
Sound off!
Here!
I see our squad is the most represented among this group!
Well, we are the best of the best.
Can't say I'm surprised.
It's only natural they'd want you on the team!
I mean, you were basically the MVP of the whole tournament!
Hey, are you listening?
Now then, the Black Bulls!
Luck, Voltia, Noel, Silva, and Asta!
Are you present?
Here!
How's that, Yuno?
No way am I gonna let you leave me in the dust!
Even if I stumble, I'll keep going!
And then stumble again.
He is pretty good at that.
Really?
You think so?
Thanks a lot!
Wait, what did you say?!
You know it's the truth.
Okay, but I'm gonna not give it up, too!
I can vouch for the stumbling part.
Oh, Asta.
I'm so happy you and I get a chance to work together again!
Yeah!
Should be fun!
Let me introduce myself as well!
As you may know, I am Meryl Leona Vermillion,
the captain of the Royal Knights!
No way!
I didn't know she would be in charge of this thing!
Come on!
Are you guys not surprised?
No.
I had assumed it would be her.
She was the one who came to get us,
and now she's doing the roll call.
What's wrong?
Nothing!
Everything's peachy, Captain!
I swear!
Our captain really is something special!
She was the one who rallied the Crimson Lion Kings
after what happened to Captain Foygolion!
Right.
I personally wish that Tidal had gone to our captain Vongent's,
but he's busy commanding security forces in the capital,
so she'll have to do.
If anyone has a complaint, then please don't hold back!
I certainly won't hold back when I crush you for it!
Really?
Now then, let's get back to business.
After enduring a cutthroat competition,
you 16 have been selected to be a part of this team.
Assuming there are no objections,
I hereby announce myself as your leader
from this moment until the eye of the Midnight Sun is annihilated!
Yes, ma'am!
Hmm?
One, two, three...
Someone's missing.
Does he think promptness is a joke?
I'm a bit late.
Sorry, guys.
Well, well.
A class clown.
Come on, let's be reasonable.
If I'm entrusting my life to you,
I'd be stupid not to find out what you're made of.
Anyway, the pleasure's all mine.
Hey, it's you again!
Wait!
Why are you wearing a Black Bull's robe?
You!
Explain to me why you're wearing that robe right now!
Idiot.
I'm one of the Black Bulls.
Why wouldn't I be wearing the uniform?
Wow!
You're a Black Bull?
Like our Black Bulls?
That's it!
I want to know everything in detail!
All of a sudden, you got me feeling nostalgic for the old days.
I used to go around beating the daylights out of Magic Nights one by one,
and I had some pretty good reasons for doing it.
You hurt Magic Nights?
Really?
That is not okay!
Chill out.
I just told you I had a good reason for it, didn't I?
Here's what happened.
Not too long ago, I ran into this outrageous monster of a guy and ended up taking a serious beating.
What's your problem?
What's this?
I like you, so I want to give you one of these.
If you don't like it, you can toss it.
Stop playing games with me, Magic Nights.
Like I'd be caught dead in this.
Besides, I don't think you're supposed to go handing these things out like candy.
Oh, I wasn't expecting you to know that.
Well, if you ever do feel like putting it on, then be my guest.
And that's how it went down.
Captain Yami scouted me for the Black Bulls and made me an official member of the squad.
But that's not fair, Zerks!
You're obviously playing dirty!
I had to work so hard to get in!
Yeah, by the way, my name's not Zerks.
I'm Zora Ideale, and I outrank you.
What's with this Zora stuff?
Don't tell me that's your name!
If I'm not mistaken, that's exactly what I just said, runt.
Why would you lie about that?
You know what they say?
To fool your enemies, you have to start with your friends.
What?
But who's your enemy?
And are you really ranked higher than me?
That's right.
So start groveling.
Forget it!
You start apologizing!
Not cool Zerks, I mean Zulub, whatever!
My head hurts!
This is confusing!
Damn, you're a noisy little guy, aren't ya?
And this is it.
From now on, I'm gonna set my sights on being a super mage.
A real magic knight.
Here, as a souvenir of our reunion, have a rainbow stink bug.
It comes at you in waves!
Hey, it's not so bad once you're used to it.
I highly doubt that!
No, you're right!
It's burning off all my nose hairs!
You're tough!
We should spar sometime!
I'm hearing an awful lot of tipper-jabber from over here!
Sorry, ma'am!
Hey, wait.
It's just us.
Everyone else left ages ago to change into their royal knight's robes!
You mean we get special uniforms and everything?
This day keeps getting cooler by the minute!
They were designed for our fight against the Eye of the Midnight Sun, which means they'll
be exceptionally resistant to magic attacks.
Now quit wasting my time and go put yours on!
Hey, check this out!
Handsome, huh?
This thing is practically made for and I've fallen in love all over again!
I never imagined you and I would be wearing the same robe, Asta.
It's not like you'll ever hold a candle to my magic abilities.
I'm going to become the next Wizard King.
No way!
I will!
Keep dreaming.
All right!
Is everyone wearing their robes now?
Oh, it's so beautiful to think a mere man-made garment would suit a god so perfectly.
To think your narcissism would give me such a perfect dirge to puke.
They certainly make it official.
And I must say, they're awfully flattering on those of us who sport a more robust figure.
That's right!
I'm ready for anything!
I suppose they're not too terrible.
How come mine is so short?
Yours is the only one like that!
Asta, don't joke around.
But I'm not joking!
This is just how I was when I put it on!
I guess when you're half a man, you only get half a robe.
We ran out of fabric.
You see, apart from you, Lod, we ended up calling upon some extra people to help out.
Some extra people?
These magic knights may not have participated in the selection exam,
but their special skills will be indispensable.
Meet Cob Portaport and Shiram Tiam!
Shirin's stone creation magic can summon a mock-up of the enemy's hideout and give us an idea of the magic power possessed by the mages hiding inside.
And Cobb can wield the ever-useful spatial magic.
We've enlisted his support since Fen'ral Rulakase is still in recovery.
Last but not least...
Nozel Silva!
He'll be joining us as well.
My brother's here.
The Silver Eagle's captain will be fighting with us?
I'm glad we have him.
Definitely.
Having the opportunity to fight with somebody like him, it's really an honor.
I was certain you would refuse my offer.
What caused you to change your mind?
Please spare me the idle chit-chat.
I'm only acting on orders from His Majesty.
With these three, the royal knights are complete!
I'm expecting great things!
Hey!
That's not very nice of you, Nozel!
What makes you think you can just waltz in here and become one of the royal knights?
I mean, you didn't even compete in the selection exam!
A better question is why you chose to take the test in the first place despite being a captain.
Huh? I thought that was the only way in!
Salutations!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun is strong!
So we're lucky to have the help of our fearless magic knight captains, especially those who possess royal blood.
You are called the royal knights after all. Get it?
Hey, it's the king.
Let's give a warm welcome to His Majesty, King Augustus Kira Clover XIII!
Oh dear! She's terribly intimidating!
I'm not used to being addressed by my full name!
Listen well, knights!
You mustn't sully the proud name of-
As I'm sure you're aware, victory is all we need!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun is a contemptible terrorist organization!
If we don't pull it up by the roots ourselves, our nation will never know peace!
We may have successfully banded together to drive them out during the attack on the royal capital, but the cost was unspeakably great.
My fool of a brother, Fuegolion, fell for their scheme and remains bedridden to this day!
Based on what we've learned from the operatives we've captured thus far, their leader is a mage called Lict, who carries a four-leaf guimoire!
Their three mightiest fighters once made up a group called the Third Eye.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun intends to gather magic stones because they believe that doing so will allow them to be reborn into their true forms and come to possess incredible power!
They have all but three stones!
Fortunately, we've been able to recover two of them before they were located.
What's more, we've defeated the Third Eye's Veto, a wielder of beast magic.
And for now, we've deterred Fauna and her fire spirit, Salamander.
The final member of the Third Eye is the copy magic user known as Raya.
He and their leader Lict are, without a doubt, the greatest and most powerful enemies we'll face during our campaign.
Their stronghold is the last line of defense they have.
If we attack it, the enemy is likely to put up all-out resistance!
We may see some casualties, but victory will still be ours in the end!
Every life in the kingdom is at stake!
If anyone here is uncomfortable with that, then I'll kill you now and save the enemy the trouble!
Are you ready?
Now!
And now, His Majesty King Augustus, Kira Clover the Thirteen!
There's no need to raise your voice!
I'm done. Feel free to continue with your address.
Thank you.
Continue, she tells me, after she so rudely interrupted me with such a lengthy spiel.
Why, there's nothing left for me to say!
Ahem!
Well, do your best, Royal Knights!
Dismissed!
Uh...
Was that it?
Hmm.
Wait, Your Majesty!
Where do we find the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout, anyway?
Oh my!
For a vexatious commoner, he brings up a good question!
You see...
Rest assured we will be making our way to their base immediately!
Listen up!
It lies in the floating dungeon found within the strong magic region called Gravitostones!
Oh, wow! It sure is late!
Hey, Raya!
As I expected, you're wearing the same cowardly expression as usual.
Oh, come on! Don't be like that!
We should go get some drinks together!
No, forget it!
You're a lightweight!
Oh, hey! There you are!
Hello, Raya!
What took you so long?
Let me guess, waking up is a pain too now?
You're the worst!
Get off my case!
Hey, Patry!
I can see you're still clinging on to Licht like nobody's business!
He's gonna belong to a human after tomorrow's big ceremony, so you better start letting go of him!
Leave me alone, Raya. That's my choice to make, not yours.
Excuse me?
It's alright. Even after we get married, Licht will still belong to everybody.
Man, human princesses are so generous.
I'd be careful what I say if I were you, though, Tetya.
Before long, there won't be any room in his busy schedule to spend time with you.
You don't have to be so blunt about things.
Patry knows what to expect.
So what's it like, knowing that you'll be a father in a few months' time?
I can sense that the mana has blessed our lives as well.
When our child arrives, we know that your kind will welcome it.
We're quite thrilled.
This little one here is the key to our future.
The bridge to unite elves and humankind.
Congratulations, Licht and Tetya.
Congratulations!
That was odd.
What a dream.
Kind of faint, though.
It's almost time to wake up.
CLOVER GLIPS!
ROADS OF PLENTY!
PART ONE!
Wow, we get special police uniforms and everything?!
This deck keeps getting cooler by the minute!
They were designed for investigating criminal activity!
Now go and put yours on!
This doesn't feel right!
Why is mine different than all the other ones?
PART TWO!
Wow, so we get special school uniforms now?!
That's way cooler than what you gave me before!
They're made for wearing to academic institutions!
Now go and put yours on!
Hold on a second, how young do you think I am?!
PART THREE!
Wow, so we get special doctor uniforms to wear?!
I'm pretty sure it doesn't get much cooler than that!
These outfits are designed for practicing medicine!
Now go and put yours on!
PART THREE!
Really? Why can't I have a cool one?!
This might hurt...
Finally, it's time for us to fight the Midnight Sun!
No matter what, the Royal Knights are gonna protect the kingdom and everyone in it!
Black Clover, page 88!
Storming the eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout!
Our new captain is pretty strong!
And scary too!
Me too!